inspiringtravellers.com 2014-06-25

# Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy :: InspiringTravellers.com - Travel the World

Welcome to our website. **If you continue to browse and use this website you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use** , which together with our privacy policy govern InspiringTravellers.com’s relationship with you in relation to this website. The term ‘InspiringTravellers.com’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

### **All content, photos and images on InspiringTravellers.com are copyright and the property of Andrea and John Spirov**. Their use is strictly prohibited unless a payment arrangement has been made with us. Should you wish to purchase a high-resolution image or smaller file sizes for editorial or commercial use, you must contact us via email: sales [AT] inspiringtravellers [DOT] com

## The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.

  * Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.

  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.

  * This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, photographs, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

  * All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.

  * Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.

  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). **We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).** Links provided as part of guest posts, which are not written by InspiringTravellers.com, should be treated as advertising. Please fully investigate and evaluate the services of any companies or websites linked to from this site on your own prior to engaging them in any business.

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how InspiringTravellers.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. **InspiringTravellers.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.** Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. InspiringTravellers.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25 March, 2010.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name and occupation

  * contact information including email address

  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We may require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our content, products and services.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales AT inspiringtravellers DOT com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to info AT inspiringtravellers DOT com If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

_Updated 14 November 2012_

[](http://track.flexlinks.com/a.ashx?foid=1044091.241303&fot=9999&foc=2 "Hotels.com Deal of the Day - 728x90 \(728x90\)")
